(Penny:)Hey, can I stay here tonight?
Shh-shh-shh.
(Leonard:)Sheldon's asleep.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
(Penny:)Well, Howard's a complete
and total ass,
(Penny:)Bernadette's in my bed,
(Penny:)and no matter how much you
stroke Amy's hair, she bites.
(Penny:)What?
Never mind.
(Penny:)Can I stay here or not?
(Leonard:)Uh, sure.
All right.
So, how do you want
to do this?
Well, I'm not getting
in bed with him.
(Leonard:)Yeah, it is
a little like
(Leonard:)getting into
Dracula's coffin.
(Penny:)We're just gonna have
to make the best of this.
(Leonard:)Okay, when you say
"make the best of it..."
(Penny:)Sleep.
Right.
(Leonard:)So we'll just call
the middle here
(Leonard:)the Neutral Zone.
(Penny:)The what?
Star Trek.
(Leonard:)You know, the
Neutral Zone
(Leonard:)between the Federation
and the Romulan Empire.
(Penny:)Oh, okay.
(Penny:)Just like old times.